<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Morteza Zakeri - services</title><link href="https://m-zakeri.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://m-zakeri.github.io/feeds/services.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://m-zakeri.github.io/</id><updated>2025-03-20T20:30:00+03:30</updated><subtitle>PhD in Computer Science</subtitle><entry><title>Services of the Intelligent Software Engineering Laboratory</title><link href="https://m-zakeri.github.io/services-of-the-intelligent-software-engineering-laboratory.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2025-03-20T20:30:00+03:30</published><updated>2025-03-20T20:30:00+03:30</updated><author><name>Morteza</name></author><id>tag:m-zakeri.github.io,2025-03-20:/services-of-the-intelligent-software-engineering-laboratory.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Find all of our services here.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amirkabir University of Technology (Tehran Polytechnic)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Author:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.m-zakeri.ir/pages/contact-me.html" target="_blank"&gt;Morteza Zakeri&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Version:&lt;/strong&gt; 1.0 (March 2025)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This document presents a comprehensive list of services offered by the Intelligent Software Engineering Laboratory at Amirkabir University of Technology (Tehran Polytechnic). The services span multiple facets of software engineering—including testing, quality assurance, secure coding, requirements engineering, and development methodologies. The items listed herein are categorized by group, level, and service code to facilitate both clarity and ease of ordering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.m-zakeri.ir/pages/contact-me.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact and order now&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Services&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Group 1: Software Product Testing and Quality Assurance (Group Code: 1)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 1: Basic Practical Training Courses (Level 1) (Order Code: 11)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.1.1: Functional Testing of Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Testing levels, testing culture, tester roles, unit testing, integration testing, and system testing.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 111&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.1.2: Security Testing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Stress testing, fault injection, fuzz testing, penetration testing, and penetration test scenarios.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 112&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.1.3: Performance Testing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Basic testing, smoke tests, load testing, stress testing, capacity testing, load increase, stability assessment, breaking point determination, rapid change and stress testing, performance evaluation metrics, and performance test scenarios.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 113&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 2: Advanced Practical Training Courses (Level 2) (Order Code: 12)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.2.1: Advanced Software Testing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Mutation testing, regression testing, model-based testing, model-driven testing, continuous testing, testing and evaluation of machine learning models (Software 2.0), test suite augmentation and optimization, and super testing.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 121&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.2.2: Automated Software Testing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Automated test generation, injection and monitoring of test data, random-adaptive testing, search-based testing, symbolic (execution) testing, and concrete-symbolic (execution) testing.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 122&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.2.3: Software Debugging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Dynamic analysis, spot analysis, fault localization, fault prediction, and program repair.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 123&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.2.4: Deployment of Tools for Testing, Debugging, and Dynamic Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Identification and deployment of tools, frameworks, platforms, and studios for testing, debugging, and dynamic analysis.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 124&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 3: Customized Training in Software Testing and Quality Assurance (Order Code: 13)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.3:&lt;/strong&gt; Customized training course—tailored selection from the above topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 4: Engineering, Consulting, and Product Development Services (Order Code: 14)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.4.1: Functional Testing for Legacy Codebases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Applicable to web, mobile, and desktop applications.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 141&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.4.2: Functional Testing for Codebases Under Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Applicable to web, mobile, and desktop applications.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 142&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.4.3: Installation and Deployment of Automated Testing Tools&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Tools installed in accordance with the product development stack (including LLM-based tools and compilers).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 143&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.4.4: Evaluation of Testing Efficiency and Estimation of Test Code Technical Debt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Measurement of testability for web, mobile, desktop, embedded systems, and Software 2.0 projects and estimation of associated technical debt.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 144&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.4.5: Optimization and Enhancement of Test Suites, and Vulnerability Remediation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Optimization and strengthening of the test suite for software projects (web, mobile, desktop, embedded systems, Software 2.0) with a reduction of test code technical debt and remediation of vulnerabilities.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 145&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.4.6: Security Testing Service&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Applicable to web, mobile, desktop, embedded systems, and Software 2.0.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 146&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.4.7: Performance Testing Service&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Applicable to web, mobile, desktop, embedded systems, and Software 2.0.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 147&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.4.8: Consulting on Quality Assurance and Testing Standards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Guidance on recognizing and implementing software product quality assurance and testing standards.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 148&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 5: Issuance of Software Product Quality Certificate (External Quality) (Order Code: 15)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.5:&lt;/strong&gt; Quality Certification Service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 6: Customized Engineering, Consulting, and Product Development in Testing and Quality Assurance (Order Code: 16)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 1.6:&lt;/strong&gt; Customized services as selected from the above topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Group 2: Software Development Quality Assurance Group (Group Code: 2)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 1: Basic Practical Training Courses (Level 1) (Order Code: 21)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.1.1: Clean Code&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Naming conventions, SOLID principles, functions, classes, comments, and code formatting.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 211&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.1.2: Clean Architecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Architecture types, architectural styles, architectural descriptions, the 4+1 view, clean architecture principles, and distance from the main sequence.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 212&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.1.3: Clean Coder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Decision-making (knowing when to say yes or no), teamwork, time management, estimation, pressure management, and version control for both product and test code.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 213&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.1.4: Secure Coding&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Data validation, authentication and authorization, encryption, session management, exception handling, meeting security requirements, and code obfuscation.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 214&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 2: Advanced Practical Training Courses (Level 2) (Order Code: 22)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.2.1: Principles and Patterns in Software Engineering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Topics include SOLID, PHAME, analysis patterns, design patterns, architecture patterns, anti-patterns, and refactoring patterns.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 221&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.2.2: Techniques for Program Transformation and Automated Software Refactoring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Program transformation, repackaging, automated refactoring, and automatic measurement of software quality attributes.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 222&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.2.3: Software Reengineering and Migration Techniques&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Software clustering, extraction and migration of software architecture, and migration to System 2.0.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 223&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.2.4: Deployment of Tools for Static Analysis and Quality Assurance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Identification and deployment of tools, frameworks, platforms, and studios for static analysis, refactoring, and ensuring the quality of software development.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 224&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 3: Customized Training in Software Development Quality Assurance (Order Code: 23)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.3:&lt;/strong&gt; Customized training course—selection from the above topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 4: Engineering, Consulting, and Product Development Services (Order Code: 24)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.4.1: Evaluation of Internal Quality Attributes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Assessing software maintainability and evolvability through metrics such as testability, understandability, reusability, readability, modifiability, flexibility, rigidity, and analyzability.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 241&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.4.2: Improvement of Internal Quality Attributes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Implementing measures to enhance maintainability and evolvability considering the aforementioned quality metrics.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 242&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.4.3: Evaluation of External Quality Attributes – Dependability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Assessment of reusability, efficiency and scalability, security, safety, reliability, and accessibility.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 243&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.4.4: Improvement of External Quality Attributes – Dependability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Enhancing reusability, efficiency and scalability, security, safety, reliability, and accessibility.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 244&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.4.5: Implementation of Design by Contract and Source Code Clean-Up&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Aligning development practices with Clean Code principles and reducing technical debt in the code.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 245&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.4.6: Refactoring of Software Design and Source Code&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Applying Clean Architecture principles to minimize design-related technical debt.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 246&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.4.7: Software Reengineering and Architectural Migration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Migrating software architecture to scalable systems while reducing architectural technical debt.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 247&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.4.8: Consulting and Mentoring on Software Quality Standards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Guidance on the implementation of standards such as ISO/IEC 25010.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 248&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 5: Issuance of Software Development Quality Certificate (Internal Quality) (Order Code: 25)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.5:&lt;/strong&gt; Quality Certification Service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 6: Customized Engineering, Consulting, and Product Development in Software Development Quality (Order Code: 26)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 2.6:&lt;/strong&gt; Customized services—selection from the above topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Group 3: Software Requirements Engineering and Development Methodologies Group (Group Code: 3)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 1: Basic Practical Training Courses (Level 1) (Order Code: 31)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.1.1: Agile Requirements Engineering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Extraction, analysis, and specification of requirements; use of requirement templates in agile software development; evaluation and improvement of requirement quality.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 311&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.1.2: Introduction to Agile Software Development Approaches&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Overview of practices such as TDD, BDD, DevOps, MLOps, and CICD.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 312&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.1.3: Management of Software and IT Projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Size and cost estimation, project status monitoring, and management of various types of technical debt.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 313&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 2: Advanced Practical Training Courses (Level 2) (Order Code: 32)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.2.1: Automated Requirements Engineering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Detection and repair of requirement smells, generation of acceptance tests, creation of conceptual models from requirements, code generation from requirements, generating explanations from code, and repair of traceability links.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 321&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.2.2: Systematic Research and Presentation in Software Engineering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Techniques such as SMS, SLR, MVLR, alongside computational thinking and reverse computation methods.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 322&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.2.3: Compiler Engineering, Large Language Models, and Domain-Specific Languages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Design and development of DSLs for specialized querying, guided engineering, and data description.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 323&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.2.4: Deployment of Tools for Requirements Engineering and Documentation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Identification and deployment of frameworks, platforms, and studios for managing requirements and project documents.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 324&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 3: Customized Training Course (Order Code: 33)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.3:&lt;/strong&gt; Customized training course—selection from the above topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 4: Engineering, Consulting, and Product Development Services (Order Code: 34)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.4.1: Extraction and Modeling of Software Requirements Documentation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Analysis and modeling of requirements for new software systems.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 341&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.4.2: Business Process Modeling (BPMN) and Creation of Services Based on System 2.0&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Utilizing large language models to innovate service creation.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 342&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.4.3: Designing Checklists and Generating Acceptance Tests for Software Validation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 343&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.4.4: Creating UML Conceptual Models from Requirements Documentation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 344&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.4.5: Database Design and Normalization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Designing and normalizing software databases in accordance with the software requirements documentation.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 345&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.4.6: Creation and Deployment of Domain-Specific Languages (DSLs)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; DSLs for development, guided engineering, and querying/reporting.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 346&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.4.7: Extraction and Repair of Legacy Code Documentation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Details:&lt;/em&gt; Addressing requirements, design, and implementation documentation for legacy codebases.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 347&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.4.8: Creation and Repair of Traceability Links for Legacy Codebases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Order Code:&lt;/em&gt; 348&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 5: Issuance of Software Requirements and Documentation Quality Certificate (Validation) (Order Code: 35)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.5:&lt;/strong&gt; Quality Certification Service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Level 6: Customized Engineering, Consulting, and Product Development in Requirements Engineering and Software Methodologies (Order Code: 36)&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service 3.6:&lt;/strong&gt; Customized services—selection from the above topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Intelligent Software Engineering Laboratory at Amirkabir University of Technology (Tehran Polytechnic) provides a diverse range of services aimed at improving the efficiency, quality, and reliability of software systems. Our offerings encompass comprehensive training courses, targeted consulting services, and custom engineering solutions that address both current challenges and future requirements in software engineering. Whether your focus is on testing, quality assurance, secure development, or requirements engineering, our expertise can help guide your organization toward excellence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Future Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, our laboratory is committed to expanding our service portfolio by:
- Integrating advanced AI and machine learning techniques into testing and quality assurance processes.
- Developing cutting-edge tools and frameworks for automated refactoring and requirements engineering.
- Broadening our training programs to include emerging methods and best practices in modern software development.
- Enhancing our consulting services to better address the complexities of legacy systems and large-scale software infrastructures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We eagerly anticipate collaborating with industry partners and academic institutions to drive innovation and excellence in software engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</content><category term="services"></category><category term="services"></category><category term="laboratory"></category></entry></feed>